Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Once upon a time, in a certain place...
Prehistoric creatures full of personality!
Tirano, Stego, Ammonite,Trilobite.
They've been saying "hi" for 500 million years.
Prehistory! Everybody Say (Roar!)
Ancient, Alright! Future, FLY High!
A herd of mammoths! Run!
Thud thud thud thud! On your marks, get set, go!
Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Dive deep into serious learning,
Playing for real.
The universe begins with passion.
Super happy!
Serious Iguanodon Museum
We are now heading on a field trip!
Where are we going?
To the Paleoart Museum!
Paleo?
And the theme is...
Iguanodon!
Now,
WELCOME TO THE WORLD OF SERIOUS PALEOTOLOGY!
Paleoart,
refers to artwork reconstructed by artists
based on the image of prehistoric creatures provided
by researchers using fossils.
First, take a look at this paleoart!
"The Country of the Iguanodon"!
Back when the world didn't know about dinosaurs yet,
in the 1830s,
one of the world's earliest paleoarts drawn was this "Country of the Iguanodon"!
Are all of these Iguanodons?
Iguanodon
Megalosaurus
Crocodile
Not quite!
Based on research at that time,
Iguanodon was thought to have a horn on the tip of its snout.
This looks good for social media!
I'll take a picture!
Fool!
Museum Matter #1!
Do not take photos of paintings without permission!
We can't take pictures?
It depends on the location.
By the way, here it's allowed!
So it IS allowed?!
What's that painting over there?
Museum Manner #2!
Follow the designated route in the museum!
Going in reverse is forbidden!
Eek, I'm sorry!
After "The Country of the Iguanodon",
next is a piece of paleoart drawn about 100 years
This is an Iguanodon too!
With the discovery of a complete skeleton
of Iguanodon in the 1870s,
its posture changed to standing upright
with its tail on the ground!
What was thought to be a horn on its nose
it was actually found to be its thumb spike,
and it's beautifully corrected in this painting!
Wait,
Tyrannosaurus also had an era like this, right?
Exactly!
Paleoart is the culmination of passion
between researchers and artists,
where artists artistically depict the results
of research at that given time!
Ah, Paleo!
What is that?
And...
after passing through all previous paleoart,
this is modern paleoart!
This one!
This artwork shows the latest Iguanodon!
Furthermore,
modern paleoart never stops evolving!
Ooh, amazing!
First, the earliest Iguanodon...
then the tail-dragging Iguanodon...
to the latest Iguanodon!
It can be said that CG is indeed the cutting edge of paleoart!
Dinosaurs...
Paleo-wesome!
Eating dinosaur chocolates
while looking at dinosaurs is the best!
What are you guys doing?!
Just snack time.
Foolish!
Museum Manner #3!
Eating and drinking inside the museum is strictly prohibited!
It seems the charm of paleoart
hasn't reached you guys at all.
So what?
In that case welcome...
welcome to the world of serious paleoart!
To truly understand the charm of paleoart,
becoming paleoart yourself is the best way!
Hehehe! Ha ha ha!